Should not have to overwrite it and read and type it in the case.
What does it mean for our customers that we use AI?
By using AI, we can increase our efficiency, precision
And quality in many different areas, not just in handling.
But we can also detect deviations such as a contribution breach
And when we use AI in the handling we have been able to see
That we reduce the risks of we miss and misunderstand information.
We make more equivalent judgments and
We also reduce unnecessary supplements.
There has been a huge shark around Chat GPT.
And we are many who have tried this AI bottom and authored texts for us.
The advantage they have is that we have this traceability based on that way
We have built it around this
Monitoring machine learning process so that we can correct.
We do follow -ups and we
can correct if we see that errors come in.
And then it is also the case that the AI solution does not make a decision without
It is always the manager who is in the end and makes the decision.
It's just a support.
If we should say a little about the future.